Center for Community Studies; Records ua652.004
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Activities and Programs, 1825-1976; 2; 12 cubic ft.
  - Community Analysis, 1962-1967 (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 53)
  - Community Colleges and Institutes, State University of New York, Undated (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 54)
  - Community Leadership and Development, 1952-1954 (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 55)
  - Community Legal Rights Foundation, Inc., 1972 (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 56)
  - Community Research, 1962 (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 57)
  - Community Resources for Education, 1952-1953 (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 58)
  - Community Studies, 1953-1957 (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 59)
  - Community Study Core Report, 1963-1964 (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 60)
  - Community Study and Development, Undated (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 61)
  - Comparative Education Society, 1968 (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 62)
  - Comparative Education Society, 1968 (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 63)
  - Conference on College-Community Relations, 1953 (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 64)
  - Conference on General Education, Cortland, 1951 (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 65)
  - Conversation in the Disciplines, 1967 (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 66)
  - Cornell University Extension Division, 1952-1953 (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 67)
  - Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 68)
  - Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 69)
  - Correspondence, 1951-1958 (Box 2 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 70)
  - Correspondence, 1951-1958 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1952-1958 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1952-1976 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 6)
  - Cortland State Teachers College, 1951-1952 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 7)
  - Costello, Thomas, Undated (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 8)
  - Council for Administrative Leadership, 1963 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 9)
  - Council of Community Services Projects, 1950-1953 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 10)
  - Council of Jewish Women, 1952 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 11)
  - The Council of Educational Needs, 1957-1958 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 12)
  - Counselor Personality, Undated (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 13)
  - Courses, 1938 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 14)
  - Courses, 1945-1957 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 15)
  - Courses, 1950-1952 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 16)
  - Courses, 1950-1952 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 17)
  - Courses, 1950-1952 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 18)
  - Courses, 1950-1952 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 19)
  - Courses, 1951-1966 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 20)
  - Courses, 1952-1953 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 21)
  - Courses, 1954 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 22)
  - Courses, 1956-1957 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 23)
  - Courses, 1958 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 24)
  - Courses, 1958 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 25)
  - Courses, 1959-1961 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 26)
  - Courses, 1961-1962 (Box 3 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 27)
  - Courses, 1961-1965 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 1)
  - Courses, 1963-1966 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 2)
  - Courses, 1964-1967 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 3)
  - Courses, 1966 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 4)
  - Courses, 1966 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 5)
  - Courses, 1966-1971 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 6)
  - Courses, 1969-1970 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 7)
  - Courses, 1972-1974 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 8)
  - Courses, Undated (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 9)
  - Courses, Undated (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 10)
  - Courses, Sociology Problems, 1963-1965 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 11)
  - Student, Paper, Undated (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 12)
  - Student, Education Philosophy 601, 1976 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 13)
  - Cummings, E, Undated (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 14)
  - Curriculum Conference, 1963 February 12 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 15)
  - Davis, Herbert, 1951 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 16)
  - Davis, John A, Undated (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 17)
  - Day, E, Undated (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 18)
  - Definition of the Field of Community Studies, 1952 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 19)
  - Department of Education, 1951-1953 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 20)
  - A Descriptive Analysis of Amsterdam, New York, 1963 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 21)
  - A Descriptive Analysis of Amsterdam, New York, 1963 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 22)
  - Developments in Education in the 1960s, 1960-1962 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 23)
  - Disney, M., M. Reiss, and B. Sherman, "The Community-Centered School", 1952 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 24)
  - Dissertation Abstracts, 1956 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 25)
  - Dissertation for the Years, 1959-1963 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 26)
  - Dissertation Requirements, and Procedures, in Educational Administration, 1963 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 27)
  - Doctoral Dissertation Committee, Student, 1960-1965 (Box 4 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 28)
  - Doctors of Education Program, 1964-1967 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 1)
  - Doctoral Program, 1963-1967 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 2)
  - Donley, D.T., The Administrator and Communication, 1960 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 3)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 4)
  - Student, 1956 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 5)
  - Student, 1957 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 6)
  - East Greenbush Adult Education Department, Undated (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 7)
  - East Greenbush School Registration, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 8)
  - Eastern New York Regional TEPS Conference, 1963 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 9)
  - Education Department Committee Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 10)
  - Education 20 Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 11)
  - Education-Industry Cooperation, 1952 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 12)
  - Education Programs, Undated (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 13)
  - Education Questions and Statements, Undated (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 14)
  - Educational Administrative, 1961-1963 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 15)
  - Educational Administrative, 1961-1963 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 16)
  - Educational Administrative, 1962-1966 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 17)
  - Educational Alliance, 1953-1954 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 18)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 19)
  - Student, Transfer of Training, Undated (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 20)
  - Ethnics and Issues Facing Teachers, 1952-1954 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 21)
  - Evaluation of Wallingford Schools, Connecticut State Department of Education, Undated (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 22)
  - The Exploratory Group for the Center for Community Studies, 1950 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 23)
  - The Exploratory Group for the Center for Community Studies, 1950 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 24)
  - Faculty Questionnaire Analyses, 1950 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 25)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 26)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 27)
  - Student, 1965 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 28)
  - The Ford Foundation Teacher Education Proposal to Arkansas, 1952 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 29)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 30)
  - Foundation of Education Department, 1974-1975 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 31)
  - Student, Culture and Personality the Psychosocial Approach to a Democratic Social Order, Undated (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 32)
  - Student, Educational Leadership and Administrative Competencies, Undated (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 33)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 34)
  - Fredonia Project, 1952 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 35)
  - Student, 1963 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 36)
  - Fundraising Information, Undated (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 37)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 38)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 39)
  - Geneseo Project, 1952 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 40)
  - Student, Soc. 480, 1961 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 41)
  - Get out the Vote Campaign, 1952 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 42)
  - Gloversville Workshop, 1953-1954 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 43)
  - Student, 1976 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 44)
  - Guide for Students: Handbook of Procedures Followed in the Programs of Advanced Studies in Educational Administration, 1962 (Box 5 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 45)
  - Hadlock, R., 1957 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 1)
  - Harpur College, 1951 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 2)
  - Healthcare and Hospitals, Photographs, 1955 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 3)
  - Health and Dental Hygiene, Photographs, 1955 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 4)
  - High School Diplomas in New York State, 1958 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 5)
  - Hillz Knowlton Resources Directory, Undated (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 6)
  - Hillsdale Center, Future Plans, 1957 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 7)
  - Historical Materials, 1910-1922 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 8)
  - History of Education Society, 1969 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 9)
  - Holliday, Al, 1965 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 10)
  - Humanities Seminar for School Administrators: Loyalty, 1964-1965 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 11)
  - Huntington, Edward F., Undated (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 12)
  - Individual, Community and Symbolism, Undated (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 13)
  - Industrial and Labor Relations Conference at Cornell, 1951 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 14)
  - Inglis, Robert D., 1957 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 15)
  - Institute of Applied Arts and Sciences at New York City, Brooklyn Institute, 1951 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 16)
  - Institute on Community Leadership, 9th Annual, 1953 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 17)
  - Intergroup Studies Projects, 1946 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 18)
  - Interim Report of the Director Center for Community Studies, New York State College for Teachers, 1950-1951 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 20)
  - Intermountain Indian School, Utah, 1952-1953 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 21)
  - Interracial Council, Albany, 1951-1952 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 22)
  - Is My Educational Philosophy Conservative or Progressive?, 1951-1952 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 23)
  - Student, Building Better Relations with Business, 1952 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 24)
  - Jackman, William M., 1957 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 25)
  - Jeffers, Verne, "Projecting Pupulation Trends in a School District,", 1961 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 26)
  - Jewish Community Center, 1950-1951 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 27)
  - Junior Red Cross, 1953-1954 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 28)
  - Keir, Charles W., 1965 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 29)
  - Kelley, Robert, 1965 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 30)
  - Kenwood Mills Project, 1951 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 31)
  - Kimball, Kenneth R., 1961 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 32)
  - Kingston Public Schools Second Mid-year Conference, 1951 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 33)
  - Kohn, Elizabeth Bell, 1957 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 34)
  - Lake Placid Conference, 1952 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 35)
  - Language Center Project, Undated (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 36)
  - Lansingburg Conference, 1951 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 37)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 38)
  - Student, 1964 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 39)
  - Leaders Conferences, 1954 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 40)
  - Leadership Training Conference, 1955 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 41)
  - Leigh, Edward, 1951 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 42)
  - Leonard, Gregory, 1976 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 43)
  - Liaison Group to Programs of Advanced Studies in Educational Administration, Undated (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 44)
  - Student, 1957 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 45)
  - Log Education 317, 1950-1951 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 46)
  - Log Sociology 110, 1950-1951 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 47)
  - Logs, 1952 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 48)
  - Student, 1975 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 49)
  - Student, 1971 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 50)
  - Student, 1976 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 51)
  - Student, 1976 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 52)
  - Student, Undated (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 53)
  - Student, "Sydney Smith: A Study of His Writings on Education", Undated (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 54)
  - Student, "Sydney Smith: A Study of His Writings on Education", Undated (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 55)
  - Student, Notebook, 1964-1965 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 56)
  - Student, Undated (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 57)
  - Memoranda, 1964 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 58)
  - Middle Atlantic States Philosophy of Education Conference, 1952 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 59)
  - Student, 1954 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 60)
  - Student, Research Project, 1956 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 61)
  - Moral Aspects of Education, Undated (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 62)
  - Moral Education, Undated (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 63)
  - Student, 1976 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 64)
  - Musella, Donald, "Open-Closedmindedness as a Factor in the Rating of Teachers by Administrators,", 1964 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 65)
  - The National Conference of Christian and Jews, 1950-1953 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 66)
  - National Conference of Professors of Educational Administration, 1963 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 67)
  - National Council for the Social Studies, Undated (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 68)
  - National School Public Relations Association, 1983 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 69)
  - The Nature and Sources of Educational Objectives, 1938 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 70)
  - NDEA, 1966-1968 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 71)
  - Neighborhood Studies, 1951-1953 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 72)
  - New Berlin Central School Project, 1951-1952 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 73)
  - New Paltz Action Research, 1952-1953 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 74)
  - News Clippings, 1949-1953 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 75)
  - New York State Association of Councils and Chests, 1958 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 76)
  - New York State Citizens Councils, 1952-1953 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 77)
  - Niles, Paula, " Philosophy of Education", 1976 (Box 6 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 78)
  - Notes, 1948 (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 1)
  - Notes, 1962-1964 (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 2)
  - Notes, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 3)
  - Notes, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 4)
  - Notes, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 5)
  - Notes, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 6)
  - Notes, Americanization, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 7)
  - Notes, Americanization, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 8)
  - Notes, Americanization, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 9)
  - Notes, Americanization, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 10)
  - Notes, East Side of New York, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 11)
  - Notes, Educational History, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 12)
  - Notes, Educational History, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 13)
  - Notes, Honors Programs, 1961 (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 14)
  - Notes, Immigrants, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 15)
  - Notes, Immigrants, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 16)
  - Notes, Social Aspects of Education, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 17)
  - Off Campus Student Teaching, 1953 (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 18)
  - Student, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 19)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 20)
  - Papers, Islam, 1972 (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 21)
  - Partial Bibliography for "Community, Society, and the Schools", Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 22)
  - Philip Livingston Project, 1954-1955 (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 23)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 24)
  - Phinney, J.T., 1964 (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 25)
  - Photosgraphs, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 26)
  - PICT, 1967 (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 27)
  - Student, 1976 (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 28)
  - Plan for Research and Writing Project to Take Place during the Six-Week Summer Session, 1952 (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 29)
  - Plattsburgh State Teachers College, 1951-1952 (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 30)
  - Pollak, Peter, The Intercollegiate Socialist Society, Student, Undated (Box 7 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 31)
  - Poliomylitis Vaccine Project, 1956 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 1)
  - Poliomylitis Vaccine Project, 1956 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 2)
  - Poliomylitis Vaccine Project, 1956 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 3)
  - Poliomylitis Vaccine Project, 1956 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 4)
  - Poliomylitis Vaccine Project, 1956 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 5)
  - Potsdam State Teachers College, Undated (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 6)
  - Preliminary Report of the Committee Appointed by the Council of Community Services, 1955 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 7)
  - Preliminary Report on the TV Course Geography 4, 1956-1957 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 8)
  - Present Status and Future Plans for the Center for Community Studies, 1951-1953 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 9)
  - Presidents Conference at Fredonia, 1951 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 10)
  - Principalship Specialization, 1963 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 11)
  - Programs of Advanced Studies in Educational Administration, 1963 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 12)
  - Proposal of a Cooperative Research Foundation of the State University of New York, 1953 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 13)
  - Progress Report of the Center for Community Studies, 1954-1955 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 14)
  - Proposal for a Conference on Community Studies and Intergroup Relations, 1953 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 15)
  - Public Opinion Study, Undated (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 16)
  - Public Relations, Photographs, 1955 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 17)
  - Public Services of the Units of the State University, 1954 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 18)
  - Publicity, 1950-1953 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 19)
  - A Proposed Project to Improve Instruction in the Early College Years, 1965 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 20)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 21)
  - Recreational Needs of the Arbor Hill Clinton Square Area, 1952 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 22)
  - Regents in New York State, 1956 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 23)
  - Religious Study, 1952 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 24)
  - Report of Amsterdam Meeting, 1962 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 25)
  - Report Casework Committee, 1950 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 26)
  - Report of the Conference of Representatives of the New York State Teachers College on Grants-in-Aid, 1951 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 27)
  - Report of the Graduate Council, 1964 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 28)
  - Report of the Meeting of the State University Committee on Community Studies, 1956 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 29)
  - Report of the Planning Conference on Community and Intergroup Relations in Teachers Education, 1951 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 30)
  - Report on the Conduct and Utilization of TV Geography 4, Undated (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 31)
  - Report on Cortland Conference, Original Notes and Copies, 1951 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 32)
  - Report on Doctoral Colloquium, January 17, 1963 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 33)
  - Report on the Present Status of the Center for Community Studies and Recommendations, 1953 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 34)
  - Report on Proposed Graduate Programs in History and Philosophy of Education, Undated (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 35)
  - Report on the Task Force of Institution, Undated (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 36)
  - Revised Rating Scale for Advanced Program Students, 1961 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 37)
  - Student, Dissertation Proposal, 1966 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 38)
  - Student, Philosophy of Education 601, 1976 (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 39)
  - Saint Adalberts School, Undated (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 40)
  - Saint John the Evangelist School, Undated (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 41)
  - Saint Luke's School, Undated (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 42)
  - Saint Luke's School, Undated (Box 8 (2-Activities and Programs), Folder 43)